One should spend time with Payal.
Armaan just pretends.  Yesterday I had a
fire in the power circuit.  There is a tower.  I turned
off the gas to the entire building.  I have visited
your sister a lot and Rudra doesn't know what she
feeds him.  When you type all this,
they must be having a lot of fun.  Because
Papa had given money to the pilot to
do all this.  I was just sitting at home and throwing in the words, '
Jo Ghar Pe Chhorandi [Music]
Kaam Karunga'.  I will name Maa Babu.
Hello everyone, how are you all?  Welcome back
to our new vlog.  Guys, brother I thought that
Lakshya is going to her home, before that I should
sit with her and read some comments
because when a person reads comments alone, it is difficult to
understand, he reads the comment as well and
he also replies, then it gets a little confusing,
so brother I thought of
taking out some comments, one from the flight vlog, one from
Chiku's father's Payal vlog on which
Payal was made to feel special,
I took out comments from both, okay the first comment is
from Harman, Payal di you are very strong,
Arman sir calls you old, I do
n't like it, Payal di you are very sweet,
always be happy, so the
relationship between husband and wife, apart from that of husband and wife, there is
also a relationship of friends
and I feel that when you
live in a friends' relationship and
come into a husband-wife relationship, then it is
better.  It is not that
you should be afraid that he is your husband and you should
not say anything or something like that should happen.  I
think we should have fun with each other.
So brother, nowadays we have also started
calling Armaan ji old, yes,
40 year old old man, clumsy old man,
we also say all these things to him.  So I feel like we should have fun.
So next
day Neha is feeling very good after seeing Tuba.
You went on a trip after a long time, did
n't you? You went to Mumbai after a long time when we were
going to Mumbai during Bigg Boss.
And when she went to Devgund with you,
not for a trip. I am talking about Babu. She was sitting when she was four
months old and now she is sitting when she is about to turn four. It has been a
long time since Tuba did not go.
She feels like staying at home.
She likes staying at home.
Our next comment is Armaan
likes staying with Zad and Kritika. He
enjoys it a lot. It is clearly visible that he has gone with Payal and her kids out of
compulsion. So
I don't understand. Guys, when you
type all this, they must be having a lot of fun with whatever goes on
in your house. You
cannot say anything about yourself.  I am not showing you my life.
We have been
showing you everything on social media for the last eight years.
Despite that you say that it does
n't feel like that with Payal's children.  Brother, they are
our children.  I have children.  Our
entire family lives together and I am tired of
answering.  If Payal goes then
you speak.  If it doesn't go then you say it.
Brother, according to me no one should motivate you.  But there
is no motivation at all.  Keep motivating.  He will either keep
talking to Armaan ji or to
me for 24 hours.  Maybe someone might have
something in mind, I will post it by commenting,
yes brother, it is like this,
next is Anveen's Payal is great, she is positive
in this situation, Payal did not know anything,
I got a call from Cheeku Papa saying, Golu,
Payal did not know anything, do
you know our flight is getting shaken, this is happening,
Payal was sitting comfortably and chilled, I said
okay, it is right that she was positive, it is
important for a person to be positive in a situation, she had children with her, if they too would have got
scared,
if she too would have got scared then what would have happened,
next is Reena's, if he goes with Golu, he
always sits with him, he
never sits with Payal, so let me tell you, I will put the
link of the Goa vlog in this vlog, go to the end and
tap and see, when we were going to Goa,
Armaan ji was sitting at the back, I was sitting in the front
and the children were sitting with me,
I was not sitting with Armaan ji, the
children were sitting with me, so we were also
sitting separately, we did not go on any honeymoon
And this is the second thing, these tickets were booked on the spot,
yes it was booked in the morning, on the spot, so as
soon as we got the tickets, the
seats that were available were booked, right? No, I
mean, you people are saying that if it happens
with Kritika, then he sits with Kritika, then
he was not sitting with me either.
We also had seats in front and behind us, when we went to Goa,
three on this side, three on this side, something like this.
Next is Hijla's Armaan is my most
favourite, I am so happy Tuba. Finally, Tuba
went on a trip with her mom and dad, Chiku Bhai, after so many days, you
said it right, it had been a long time since Tuba's trip,
Chiku had also not gone to Goa, Chiku had also not gone, it
seems Chiku did not go to Goa, Ayan had also gone, Zad had also gone,
you had also gone,
I had also gone, Chiku had not gone to Goa, so it is a
good thing that Chiku had gone, he has come back after
enjoying a bit, Shagun Bhaiya's, it was fine,
he was with him, he left, Shagun Bhaiya, I am
talking for you, next is Jasan's
Payal, she is looking so beautiful.  She looks like Chiku's elder
sister.  What did I say yesterday?   The
beans were growing yesterday.  I told you so and guys I did
not read this comment.  I told you last night itself.
A photo of Payal
came yesterday.  I was always sitting.  Payal's photo
came.  Payal was wearing a white top.  Black
Shots have also sat down.  I said Payal,
Lakshya looks like Payal's brother.   It doesn't seem to be working.  It's
exactly the same.  Height is also
same, almost weight is also everything is same.  So it
is absolutely similar.  The appearance is also the same.
Next is friend, work should be done in this situation.
You have created such an issue.  So let
me tell you the same.  We are
bloggers.  Blogging means that
you show your real life.  You do
n't show anything other than that, you don't fake it.
If there is turbulence in the flight,
if there is any problem in the flight, then
Hanuman ji will show it to you.  It is
not like we are sitting in a flight for the first time.
Ok?  How long will life be while sitting?  I do
n't even know how many flights I have taken.  It has
always been a good experience.
Sometimes, even if something is bad once in a 100 years, a
person will share it, right?  So I don't
think he has done anything wrong.  He has
shared his life.  Look at the place where the incident happened, there are a
lot of people sitting there.   There are
100 people sitting in the lot.
One person out of 100 is a blogger.  So brother, he will do vlogging.
His job is blogging.
Next is Priyanka's Payal, you are the
strongest woman in the universe, very
positive, be positive always, this is true, you are
absolutely strong, Payal, so guys, just now I got a
video call from Chiku's father and they are having a lot of
fun, enjoying
because father has gone to some place, has he gone to the
beach, there is a party going on,
okay, so I thought in my mind, I said friend,
we had gone, but we had not seen it, I had
seen, they were having such a party, where should
we go, where should we go, so friend, really friend, the guys are with us,
because father
said absolutely right that this time
their trip is very fun, this is
absolutely right, as a person goes to the same place
two-three times, he gets
experience.  Like now if I
go to Dubai, I know about Dubai, where to
visit, where not to visit, what to do, I
know everything.  So this is the matter and the same is being
discussed with Payal right now.  Tuba is
looking very cute today.  Tuba is wearing a very beautiful
dress because how can I comment
because Payal Laksh I don't know about
Instagram.  People were commenting on Lakshya's Instagram
that you did
not keep Tuba well maintained.  This Tuba is
not looking beautiful.  What clothes is Tuba
wearing?  And today Tuba is wearing very nice
clothes.  It is not Payal's fault either, friend.
Suba said that he booked tickets to Goa on the
spot.  I am thankful to Laksh that
we have a luggage which I
showed you yesterday in which there are more clothes, so
inside it we
keep at least six sets of children's clothes, not more.
Chiku also has five to six new pairs, which means every
child in our house has six to seven
new pairs.   So, assume that you
woke up at 11:00.
Yes, I left at 1:00.  She left at one or two o'clock.  There was
no packing system.   Got it
packed on the spot.  So this is the same
look I have, do you know what it is guys.  You
neither see what you see nor do you act on it.  You
Payal have gone to the gym.  I did all the packing from behind.
But I didn't make a full vlog of what
I was packing.   I am
packing.  But brother,
you comment on whatever you see.  Okay, it was a
very funny vlog.
You all stay happy like this.  Payal didi is happy, Armaan bhai, I
pray for you too.  Your family is very nice.
Ayan Jaan is here, just roam around like this.  Payal didi is
very nice with children.  Thank
you so much.  Absolutely fine.  You
said exactly the right thing.  What is it now, our
life has become like this.  The children grew up.
Gradually the children grew up.  So we
cannot move around comfortably like this.  Earlier, when the children were small, there was
tension.  But what happens now is that
Payal and I can roam around comfortably.  Sometimes
Payal goes away and sometimes I go away.  Sometimes the children
go with Chiku's father.  Come with us sometime.
We can make many trips.
Next is Finally Tuba Got Her
Chance.  Of course she is enjoying her trip
but sometimes I feel that she is missing the children.
She is missing the children.  She is
missing Ayan a lot.  Then she is
missing the kids.  Next is
why did Payal not take Rudra with her?  He is a small baby.   Let's do it like this.
Gather the whole family and take
Sara away.   Nothing will be
visible in that too.   Nothing will be
visible in that also.  Look, let me
tell you about Rudra.  When Rudra
goes to the farm, he becomes completely red.  That causes
all the rashes.  Now the weather in Goa is
very rainy there.   It
is completely humid.   It
is so humid.  A child gets bitten by an insect.
Some people will then tell the child that you are carrying such a small
child.  Golu was at home, we could
not give it to her.  Remember last
time my friend fell ill.   Oh,
how sick I was.
He had a high fever.  Brother, he had a very high fever, after
giving medicines overnight, that boy was like this.
That child was so sad during the entire trip, he had high fever for two days
but we took him to Goa.  What do we do
?  We had our tickets.  So brother Rudra is with me.
Absolutely fine.  He is happy.  Armaan
Uncle, Payal Aunty, Kritika Aunty, Laksh Didi,
Lakshmi Didi [laughs]
I am younger, right?  I look bigger than tea.
But no no,
I look older to you.  Payal
looks the youngest.  Tubayan zad ruda chiku
so beautiful.  Payal I was watching your old vlogs.  She was
commenting.  You never read my comments.
Thank you so much.  I
read your comment and you
wrote with so much love.  Do you know what Choti's guys talk about
?  When a person's height is neither a little longer
nor a little more.  So it automatically
looks bigger.  Whose height is neither
short nor thin.  Thin and so he
looks small.  Payal will not grow old forever, even in old age.
I will come as soon as possible.  If we compare then
I will grow old quickly.  My face will
age quickly.  It will not fit on Payal.
Because Payal Na will look young.  The cheek
looks something like this.  Next is Har Har Mahadev.  Hats
off to Armaan sir.  You motivated the situation.
This is the best blogger.  The
motivation he provided was of a different level.
No one could really do it.  Next is
Ankita's Armaan You Should Know This Payal Is A
Lucky Charm For Your Family.  Wherever she goes, she
brings positive vibes.  She is a strong and
confident lady.  It is born with complete details and full
explanation.  One should
spend time with Payal.  Armaan just
pretends.  Brother, I don't understand.
I don't understand.  Guys why do you guys say that
he is showing off.
Where should the poor man go?  Whatever he is in his situation,
he is absolutely fine.  He
sees everything.  Look at your children.   Let's look at
our family.  They are taking us forward.
He taught blogging to our entire family.  Meaning, whatever that
man does, he is treating me like a single person.   I am
singing.  Went into the singing line.   I
told the children about family, team and everything and gave them money.   Isn't it that you
handle everything yourself?
Whether it is for the team, whether it is a situation at home
, or any situation outside.   There are
many problems going on
in life, I am handling them all myself.   He is
also handling the children himself.  So let me
read the next comment, Simran
Gupta.  Bua's vlog with Payal and Tuba
became interesting as she gave both of them princess
treatment.  Dress Tuba in beautiful clothes.
Shopping for special cute clothes for Tuba.  Tuba has not
gone anywhere.  Please make her feel very good and special.
Both father and daughter will enjoy it.   Please
upload two videos of Goa daily.
Payal Arman Tuba.  First of all,
before leaving he had said that we are just
going for a walk and maybe Vogs might not come.  But he's
still posting vlogs.  Everyone had
planned this for Tuba at home
while packing that we will take very few clothes from here.  We will
buy colourful clothes from there and by
wearing colourful Goa clothes there, we have to make Tuba
feel special in front of Papa.
Less clothes were taken from here.
Less clothes have been taken from here.  Tuba was
wearing such a beautiful dress right now.  How beautiful she looked with it
tied from behind.  And in fact,
we didn't even make Zad and Ryan
wear anything.  We had made him
wear that red coat set.   I had
taken only one set of clothes.
Yes, I had bought the same clothes.  I will
show you the clothes now.  Ok.  Next
is Golu Zad's evil eye on the trip.  What happened
to Chiku's father did not happen.
Like me, he got my and Zad's evil eye,
I was blowing the difference while sitting at home.
Who cast an evil eye on the house that was on fire and all these things?   Do
n't know who cast the evil eye on me?  You must have got it.
[laughter]
One is I Am Pilot.
She comes here again later.
I am a pilot.  All this happens because of the wind.  It
moves very fast outside.  Yes, disturbance occurs
due to wind.  You said it absolutely right.
Look [sound of clearing throat] you're the
pilot.  You are a pilot.  You are used to it.  We are
not used to it.  We are sitting on the same flight
sometimes.
We are sitting in the clouds, so it happens in the clouds.  It
moves a little bit.  But suddenly becoming like this.   The
fear is getting worse.  To get a shock.   Falling down
again and again.
And stay in the air for an hour.  Dude is human.   Will get scared.  I am dying.  The
family is sitting.   There
is no network.  Some have
no network.  No one
can make a call.  I am sitting here thinking that
Payal Chiku Papa has not arrived.  Nothing,
how late it is, it has not reached, how late it is, it has
not reached, it is something that is tensed brother, this is
original, it is not scripted, no guys,
this was a complete scripted vlog, Chiku's father had
given money to the pilot to do all this so that it becomes a
vlog, he was a very good pilot,
listened to Chiku's father, you should also do it like this next
time, if you are going somewhere then do it like this,
next thing is do
travel by train, it is safe brother,
train is safe but now sometimes trains also
overturn, it is a
matter of luck, there is nothing greater than luck,
guys trains also overturn,
people's vehicles get damaged, so
many times trains also meet with accidents, God forbid something like this should happen, trains
also meet with accidents.  Well, when Payal goes out to meet
Armaan, some problem or the other occurs in Golu's house.
Gaius was
absolutely right.  Yesterday I had a
fire in the power circuit.  I felt like it.  It had been a long time.
I did not spend any money.  So
I thought ₹200 ₹1200 money has been collected.
O I first set fire to the power circuit.
Then what did I do?  You will believe guys, there are
B1, B2, B3, B4 towers in my society.
I turned off the gas to the entire building.
Your sister has a lot of influence.  [laughs] I have a
lot of reach.  I feel like it today.  Today
I am happy guys because my
makeup stuff has come back from NYC.  So I have to
unbox it quickly.  I am very happy.  These
are my makeup items.  Ok?   I was
just giving it like that.  So I quickly
closed all the gas societies.  Then
I called the Adani people.
I told the Adani people to turn
off the gas for 24 hours.  Then he messaged me.
Send a message to the entire society.  Then
my manager from the society sent me a
message saying, you are informed that the
Adani gas pipeline has been damaged.
On Ambala Chandigarh Highway.  We will repair it
and your gas will arrive by 9:30.
So she went at 6:00 in the evening.  Then he
said 9:30, after 9:30 he
said 6:00 in the morning and now he said 6:00 in the evening, so it is going to be
24 hours.  So I do
all this from behind.  I don't know
what I will do tomorrow, I can reach tomorrow, right?
Or I'll do something else tomorrow.  I will see what
comes to my mind.  Now the next one is Lakshya,
please answer it.  Rudra does
n't know what she drinks or feeds him.
Rudra drinks only milk.  He
remains happy in his own world.  Whether he stays at home or on the farm.
He is a very cool kid.  He neither cries
nor troubles.  Nothing.  He enjoys
drinking milk.  He sleeps.  Does.  Just yes.  And
I am handling it well.  Don't
worry at all.  So guys, here I
called Ayan.  I am not showing his photo to Ayan.
We enjoyed Goa so much, a
lot inside Goa.  This
photo was clicked by Laksh.  Son, this is the medicine.
Look Anu, look this one of yours, should I
show you Anu your photo from Goa?  Anu
also bathed in the pool.  Do you know
what you did in the pool?  You did it, do you
know how much you enjoyed it guys?  Look,
I had dressed both the children in the same clothes.
These are all my photos from Goa.
So guys let's just end this comment.
See you in the next vlog.  Bye
guys, take care, everyone.